ANDRIY NOSOV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER





+38(067) 909 86 40



nosovandriy@gmail.com



t.me/NosovAndriy



github.com/nosovandriy



linkedin.com/in/andriy-nosov



andriynosov.com



Ternopil, Ukraine | Remote

HARD SKILLS

- JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS
- React, React Native, Next.js
- SCSS, Tailwind, MUI, Bootstrap
- Redux Toolkit. Zustand
- Rest API, SQL, Git, NPM
- · AWS, Vervel, Postman, Github
- Figma, Jira, SEO, UX/UI

EDUCATION

 Master's degree in Computer Engineering

Ternopil Ivan Puluj National Technical University | 2010

· Frontend development

Mate Academy | 2022

LANGUAGES

- English B1 (Intermediate)
- Unkrainian Native

ABOUT ME

As a frontend developer, I have a degree in computer engineering and experience with a stack of technologies, including JavaScript, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, React, Next.js, Redux, Rest API, and others.

I have over a year of experience working on commercial projects, both individually and in a team. You can check all of the projects in my portfolio website.

I have good self-learning skills, thanks to which I was able to learn a lot of necessary technologies and use them effectively in my projects.

My English level is Intermediate, I have good communication skills, which I acquired from a previous job where I worked on a large team and communicated with many clients.

Also, I worked with export documents, which allowed the company to increase its sales and enter the world market. So I can add responsibility and attentiveness to my strong point.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer | Art vs. War Project

March 2023 - Present

- Implemented prototype of a charity online platform selling artists' paintings on the European market;
- Building the project based on Next.js and Spring Boot frameworks;
- Using services such as AWS Cognito, Amplify for authorization and deployment, and Cloudinary for image management;
- Implementing UI for the payment and shipping using Google Autocomplete, shipping API, and Stripe;
- Conducting code reviews, investigating, reproducing, and resolving bugs;
- Managing tasks and estimates in Jira following SCRUM;
- Collaborating with a team of frontend and backend developers, QA engineers, and UI/UX designers;

Frontend Developer | Freelance

August 2022 - February 2023

- Developed and designed an E-commerce store with a mobile-first orientation from scratch:
- Building the project based on the Next.js framework;
- Implemented the ability to receive order data in the Telegram bot;
- Integrated the Google Analytics service;
- Improving SEO optimization of the web store;
- Developed an information website for a logistics company with a userfriendly responsive design;
- Integrated possibilities receive information about customers' orders by e-mail;
- Integrated Google Maps and Facebook chat;

COMMERCIAL PROJECTS

A	\ A /	
Art vs	vvar -	

DESCRIPTION: The "Art vs War" gallery platform is designed to facilitate the sale of paintings, with a focus on merging art and charity. The platform offers possibilities where artists can sell their paintings. Key features of the project include user registration, artist profiles for uploading and editing paintings, and secure sales transactions. This project is based on Next.js and Spring Boot frameworks, utilizing Amazon Web Services and Stripe payment service. Our team consists of a PM, frontend and backend developers, QA, and a UI/UX designer.

TOOLS: Next.js, TypeScript, HTML, SCSS, Redux, Axios, AWS Amplify, AWS Cognito, Cloudinary, Stripe, React-hook-form.



https://artvswar.gallery



https://github.com/nosovandriy/art-vs-war



DESCRIPTION: E-commerce store with a mobile-first orientation design, built on Next.js. Implemented the ability to receive order data in the Telegram bot and integrated the Google Analytics service.

TOOLS: Next.js, TypeScript, HTML, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Axios, Swiper, Vercel, Google Analytics, Telegram bot.



https://nahirna-cake.com.ua



https://github.com/nosovandriy/nahirna-cake-store



DESCRIPTION: An information website for a logistics company with a user-friendly responsive design. Customers have the ability to request a callback, communicate through Facebook chat, and the owner can receive information about customer orders via e-mail.

TOOLS: Next.js, TypeScript, HTML, SCSS, Swiper, Facebook chat.



https://www.ukrainets.in.ua



https://github.com/nosovandriy/ukrainets

OTHER PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sales Manager | SE Chortkivskyi KHP

2016 - 2021

- Implemented the export functionality abroad, which allowed exporting products to the world market.
- Prepared export documents and delivered about 10 thousand tons of goods.

Hardware Sales Manager | Tetra Consulting

2012 - 2015

- Bought and sold computer hardware and other related equipment.
- · Worked with product vendors. Signed cooperative agreements with new suppliers and expanded the dealer network.

Computer Repair Technician | Tetra Consulting

2010 - 2012

Repaired computer hardware, built, tested, and configured PCs.